I'm gonna talk a bit about the secret
我要说说这个秘密
history and tragic fate of Sun is gun
的历史和悲惨命运是枪
safe and then Paul is going to discuss
安全，然后保罗将要讨论
some of the potential replacements for
一些潜在的替代品
at least some uses of sunless gun safe
至少有一些使用日光枪的保险柜
how many people people in this room have
这个房间有几个人
not ever written code to use sunless gun
从来没有写过使用日光枪的代码
safe Oh more than I would have expected
安全哦，超出我的预期
okay well I I don't think I need to
好吧，我不认为我需要
explain to this audience what what Sun
向这个听众解释太阳是什么
misc unsafe is but you might be
杂项不安全是，但你可能会
interested in in a little bit of its
对它的一点点感兴趣
history so it's really meant to be it's
历史，所以这真的意味着
just a low level VM library interface
只是低级VM库界面
designed strictly for use within the JDK
专为在JDK中使用而设计
you know this is a fairly common thing
你知道这是很普遍的事情
to find in advanced language
查找高级语言
implementations that are implemented you
实现了您的实现
know partly in a low-level language and
会以某种低级语言来部分了解
partly in themselves and it should be no
部分地自己，应该没有
surprise that Java has one of these two
奇怪的是Java有这两个之一
it originated we originally introduced
它起源于我们最初介绍的
it in the 1.4 release it was used for
它在1.4版本中用于
there there was a big rewrite as some of
有一些大的改写
us may recall of the entire row of all
我们可能会想起所有的整行
the reflection machinery which
反射机械
previously had been just massive
以前只是巨大的
quantities of j'ni code and very slow
j'ni代码的数量和非常慢
there's a big great rewrite of
有很大的改写
reflection we also used it to speed up
反射，我们也用它来加快
the serialization and it was used for
序列化，它用于
the the direct buffer code in new i/o in
新I / O中的直接缓冲区代码
Java 5 it was extended further being a
Java 5进一步扩展了它
principally to support jsr 166 Java util
主要支持jsr 166 Java util
concurrent the atomic and lakhs some
并发原子和lakhs一些
packages that's when you have things
当你有东西的时候
like parking on Park appeared it was
就像在公园停车一样
also used for other things for corporate
也用于公司的其他事情
performance for the 5 people who care
照顾5个人的表现
about corporate performance Nativity
关于公司业绩诞生
scaled font cache and low-level x11
缩放的字体缓存和低级x11
interface any of it the x11 interface
接口任何x11接口
for AWT you know again was originally
对于AWT，您再次知道原来是
written as a bunch of j'ni calls against
写成一堆j'ni呼吁反对
X Lib which is slow for the obvious
X Lib很明显很慢
reasons so we read it all back with with
原因，我们一起阅读
unsafe and that was a big improvement in
不安全，这是对
Java 6 more stuff in Java util
Java util中还有Java 6的更多内容
concurrent's it was also used to speed
并发的它也被用来加快
up some some crypto algorithms Java 7
一些加密算法Java 7
more lots more stuff
更多更多的东西
java.util concurrent and some other
java.util并发和其他
stuffs other other performance work Java
其他其他性能工作Java
math big decimal and big integer were
数学大十进制和大整数分别
sped up substantially by using some
通过使用一些大大加快
unsafe primitives java.lang invoke
不安全的原语java.lang调用
method handles of course used unsafe 2d
方法句柄当然使用了不安全的2d
rendering buffers and you know load
渲染缓冲区，您知道负载
average for JMX you know why is that
JMX的平均值，你知道为什么
unsafe well yeah it was a convenient
不安全，是的，这很方便
place to put it it's not actually it's
放它的地方实际上不是
not actually unsafe and neither is some
其实并不安全，也不是一些
of the other stuff in it safe to be true
可以肯定地说其他东西
to be honest and in Java oh whoa
说实话，用Java哦，哇
yet more job use concurrent stuff and
还有更多的工作使用并发的东西
it's also used in the Mac OS Objective C
它也用在Mac OS Objective C中
bridge I may have missed a few uses but
桥，我可能错过了一些用途，但
this was you know an hour of reppin
这是你知道一个小时的reppin
through our archival source code
通过我们的档案源代码
repository repositories to figure it out
仓库来解决
so like all api's in sun dot star
就像所有api在太阳点星中一样
packages some misc unsafe was never
打包一些杂项不安全从来没有
intended for external use we tried to
用于外部用途，我们试图
discourage this we had this this page
不鼓励我们拥有此页面
was originally created on Java dot Sun
最初在Java dot Sun上创建
calm this is the Wayback Machine
冷静这是Wayback Machine
February 15 1998 I think I think it was
1998年2月15日，我认为是
actually created a bit before that but
实际上在那之前创建了一点，但是
this is the earliest snapshot on the
这是最早的快照
wayback machine yet why developers
回溯机，但为什么开发人员
should not write programs that call some
不应该编写调用某些程序的程序
packages you know they are not part of
您知道它们不属于的软件包
the supported public Java interface did
受支持的公共Java接口
this stop people
这阻止了人们
no of course it didn't we did other
当然不是，我们没有做其他的
things we tried to make it at least a
我们试图使其至少
little bit hard to use by putting up a
通过放置一个有点难使用
roadblock but with the language that we
障碍，但我们使用的语言
had that we have now still there's only
如果我们现在仍然只有
so much we can do so there's this little
我们可以做的很多
hack which all admit responsibility for
所有人都承认对此负责
and hardcourt coded names in the VM
和虚拟机中的硬编码名称
right so that make it well just a bit
对，这样可以使它变得很好一点
hard to get at unsafe you have to either
很难不安全，你要么
put your coat on the boot class path or
把外套穿在靴子上
you have to do the following by now
您现在必须执行以下操作
well-known hack you know this is all
著名的黑客，你知道这就是全部
over Stack Overflow you know class for
在堆栈溢出中，您知道要上课
name son miss gunns save get the
儿子儿子冈斯小姐的名字保存得到
declared field make it accessible and
声明的字段使其可访问并且
boom you're off to the races you know as
蓬勃发展，您就参加了众所周知的比赛
you know the mere cost of this code plus
您知道这段代码的成本加上
a compiler warning which of course you
编译器当然会警告您
can also turn off if you really want
如果你真的想也可以关闭
with - XD ignore symbols file true
与-XD忽略符号文件为true
however you know so so this is this was
但是你知道，所以这是
you know it was possible to use this
你知道可以用这个
outside that was a bad thing but it was
外面那是一件坏事，但这是
also in some ways a good thing right the
在某些方面也是一件好事
work on java.util concurrent done by by
由java.util并发完成的工作
Doug Lee and his collaborators some of
道格·李（Doug Lee）和他的合作者
whom were in this room you know this
谁在这个房间里，你知道这个
after its initial release oh java.util
最初发布之后，哦java.util
concurrent continued to evolve outside
并发继续向外部发展
and this was possible because son miss
这是可能的，因为儿子想念
gun safe was accessible at you know a
您知道可以使用枪支保险柜
fair at a fairly low price and it was ok
价格相当低，还可以
right because well we trust Doug so it's
对，因为我们相信道格，所以
OK for Doug to use something that's gun
道格可以使用枪支的东西
safe in the JDK but in fact some miss
在JDK中安全，但实际上有些遗漏
gun safe was also used outside the JDK
JDK之外也使用了枪支保险柜
it's been used by a number of projects
它已经被许多项目使用
to do things that would be very
去做那些非常
difficult if not just completely
即使不是完全也很难
impossible to do outside of the JDK is
在JDK之外不可能做的是
this a bad thing well it's kind of risky
这是一件坏事，有点冒险
to base your business on an unstable
以不稳定的业务为基础
unsupported API but I think on that net
不支持的API，但我认为
it's actually a good thing it shows you
这实际上是一件好事，向您展示
it shows us how to push the platform
它向我们展示了如何推动平台
forward and demonstrates what can be
转发并演示可以做什么
done if you take the platform as it's
如果您采用平台就可以完成
officially defined and then add just a
正式定义，然后添加一个
little bit of unsafe stuff so I think
一点不安全的东西，所以我认为
that that's been healthy for the overall
对整体来说是健康的
ecosystem so you know and some of you
生态系统，所以您知道，其中一些人
send this gun safe it's it's an unsafe
安全地寄出这把枪是不安全的
abstraction extremely unsafe abstraction
抽象非常不安全的抽象
for building better faster safe
用于构建更好，更快，更安全
abstractions and it's ok
抽象也可以
you know it's use is okay in some
你知道在某些情况下可以使用
informal sense when it's in the hands of
非正式的感觉
expert developers now despite all this
尽管这一切，专家开发人员现在
son miss gun safe has been and continues
儿子小姐枪支安全已经并继续
to be an ongoing burden it's been a
成为一个持续的负担
burden for a number of reasons one is
负担有很多原因，一个是
like any API internal or otherwise it's
就像任何内部的API一样，否则
been abused it's been misused
被滥用，被滥用
there are 379 results as of yesterday
截至昨天有379个结果
on Stack Overflow people asking you know
在堆栈溢出的人问你知道
well-meaning but maybe naive developers
善意但也许天真的开发人员
asking how do I use send miss gun safe
问我如何使用发送安全小姐枪
to solve you know this problem I hear
解决你知道这个问题我听到了
it's really cool and powerful and I can
它真的很酷而且功能强大，我可以
do need stuff with it so they're you
确实需要东西，所以他们就是你
know they're you know we're scrolling
知道他们是你知道我们正在滚动
through this is is fairly entertaining
通过这是相当有趣的
here's here's an example how can I free
这是一个例子，我该如何释放
memory using using Sun Miss gun safe you
使用Sun Miss Gun记忆体可以保护您的安全
know here well here's the idiom again
知道在这里这又是成语
how to get how to get the unsafe object
如何获得不安全物体
and I'm gonna a legate something and
而且我要赠予一些东西，
omit how do I work with how do I get the
省略我如何与如何工作
address to free maybe I use the hash
免费的地址，也许我使用哈希
code we all know where this leads
我们都知道代码会导致什么
so aside from this which is just kind of
因此，除了这之外，
a you know an ongoing cost me in the
你知道一个持续不断的花费了我
overall ecosystem well it's a security
整体生态系统是安全的
issue you know the fact that that Sun is
问题，您知道Sun是
gun safe is there that it's fairly
那里有枪支保险柜
easily accessible that it's trivially
容易获得，这很简单
accessible by any code in inside the JDK
可通过JDK内部的任何代码访问
itself makes a real a strong defense
本身就构成了强大的防御
in-depth strategy harder and that's one
深入策略更难了
of our key strategies for making the
我们制定的关键策略
platform more secure is to have you know
更安全的平台是让您知道
more than one boundary around powerful
围绕强大的多个边界
operations and if if it's that easy to
操作，如果很容易
get to well what you know if you could
弄清楚你知道的如果可以的话
if you can if you can leverage a few
如果可以的话，可以利用一些
vulnerabilities to get in inside the jdk
进入jdk的漏洞
code then well some its gun safe you you
代码，然后用一些枪支使您安全
now have all the power you could
现在拥有您所能拥有的所有力量
possibly want and there's also just the
可能想要，还有
the ongoing maintenance burden so the
持续的维护负担，因此
and there's a maintenance burden borne
并且承担了维护负担
not just by those of us who work on the
不只是那些从事
jdk itself but also just the general you
jdk本身也只是一般的你
know the developers out in the world
了解世界各地的开发商
many developers wind up using unsafe and
许多开发人员最终使用了不安全的
they don't even know it right you you
他们甚至不知道对不起你
build an application you use you use
建立您使用的应用程序
maven you download half the internet
行家，您下载了一半的互联网
from maven central and you lo and behold
从Maven Central出发，您瞧瞧
you know fifteen jar files down from
你知道十五个jar文件
your actual code there's something that
您的实际代码中有一些东西
uses unsafe you don't even know about it
使用不安全的东西你甚至都不知道
now unsafe is an unstable unsupported
现在不安全是不稳定的不受支持
API if it changes your application is
如果它更改您的应用程序的API
gonna break when that happens are you
当那件事发生时你会崩溃
gonna are you believe even know that
你会相信甚至知道
that jar file fifteen levels down is the
该jar文件向下15级是
problem no you probably won't and who
问题不，你可能不会，谁
are you going to blame you're going to
你要怪你吗
blame
怪
the implementers of your Java Runtime
Java运行时的实现者
you're not going to blame the author of
你不会责怪作者
that library so because of that kind of
该图书馆，因为这种
factor that has made those of us who
使我们这些人
work on the JDK fairly reluctant to
对JDK的工作相当不情愿
evolve some this gun safe you need to
进化一些你需要的枪支安全
remove things in it that aren't they
删除其中不是的东西
aren't needed inside the JDK anymore or
在JDK中不再需要
change the behavior of existing things
改变现有事物的行为
and because we've been reluctant to
而且因为我们一直不愿意
change it has become almost a de facto
改变它几乎已经成为事实
standard thing and then more people
标准的东西，然后更多的人
start relying on it and we get where you
开始依靠它，我们可以到达您的位置
get sucked into this whirlpool of
陷入这个漩涡
dependence where where it's frozen and
依赖在哪里冻结和
we can never evolve it so how do we
我们永远无法发展它，那么我们该如何
escape this vortex in jdk 9 as part of
摆脱jdk 9中的漩涡，作为
project jigsaw we are going to move most
项目拼图，我们将最感动
internal api's inside module boundaries
内部api的内部模块边界
so there will be strongly encapsulated
所以会有很强的封装
they will not be accessible most of them
他们大多数人将无法使用
even with the set accessible trick you
即使使用设定的可访问技巧
you won't even be able to get to them by
你甚至无法通过
a reflection with the one exception that
反映了一个例外
if you're willing to use a command line
如果您愿意使用命令行
flag you can override that and that's it
标记，您可以覆盖它，仅此而已
in the long run this is what we want to
从长远来看，这就是我们想要的
do with all internal api's and this this
用所有内部api做到这一点
is what we want to do with some is gun
我们想要做的就是枪
safe we've been saying for a while now
安全，我们已经说了一段时间了
that we would do this with sundnes gun
我们将用sundnes枪来做到这一点
safe in jdk 9 that has never actually
在jdk 9中安全，实际上从来没有
been the plan the actual plan is this so
是计划，实际计划是这样
the fate of some miss gun safe this is
一些枪支安全小姐的命运，这是
in in JEP 260 which I published last
在我上次发布的JEP 260中
week is as follows in JDK 9 it will be
在JDK 9中的一周如下所示
available to code on the class path by
可通过以下方式在类路径上进行编码
default it will be available to code in
默认情况下它将可用于编码
modules by request if you decide to put
如果您决定放置模块，则可以根据要求
your code in a module you can declare
您可以在模块中声明的代码
that that module requires requires the
该模块要求的
module that contains Sun this gun safe
包含Sun的模块，此枪支安全
and you can continue to use it but
您可以继续使用它，但是
you'll be aware that you're using it it
您会意识到您正在使用它
will not be further enhanced and over
不会进一步增强和结束
time broadly used functionality and Sun
时间广泛使用的功能和Sun
this gun safe will be migrated to safer
这个枪支保险箱将被迁移到更安全
supported api's some of which Paul will
支持api，其中Paul会支持
discuss
讨论
a few moments so here's the here's the
片刻，所以这里是这里
recipe for for what will happen in which
发生什么情况的秘诀
release in a particular JDK release call
在特定的JDK发布调用中发布
it n if a supported replacement for an
如果支持的替换项，则为n
unsafe method exists in the previous
以前存在不安全的方法
release and minus 1 then we will
释放并减去1，我们将
encapsulate or remove that method in
封装或删除该方法
release n so you've got a review about
发布n，所以您对
one release to figure it out if a
一个版本，以找出是否
replacement for a method exists in that
存在一种方法的替代品
release we will deprecated that unsafe
发布我们将弃用那种不安全的方法
method in in that release and we might
该版本中的方法，我们可能
even deprecated it with a new even
甚至以新的偶数弃用了它
stronger deprecated deprecation tag
更强的弃用弃用标签
that's even more annoying
更加烦人
once replacements for all unsafe methods
一次替换所有不安全的方法
exist in the previous release some miss
在以前的版本中存在一些遗漏
gun safe will be removed gone so you
枪支保险柜将被移除，所以您
know whether whether whether the value
知道是否有价值
of n here is is 10 11 or 12 I will leave
的n个是10 11或12我将离开
to the future well that will not attempt
到将来不会尝试的井
to predict that going forward there will
预测在那里前进
canoe we will continue to have interim
独木舟，我们将继续过渡
internal api's that are deeply in bed
内置在床上的内部api
with a vm that yes sorry Marcus there
与一个对不起马库斯的vm
will be additional hard-coded names in
将是中的其他硬编码名称
the VM we will place them in packages
虚拟机，我们将它们放在包中
with the whose name is prefixed with JDK
其名称以JDK为前缀的
internal these will be encapsulated you
内部这些将封装您
will not be able to get at their
将无法达到他们的
internals except by a command line flag
内部结构，命令行标记除外
and that's that's intentional we want we
那就是我们想要的故意
want people to be aware of when they're
希望人们知道他们何时
using this we would like for people to
使用这个我们希望人们
be responsible when they use it we can't
当他们使用它时要负责任
force responsibility we can we can only
强制责任，我们可以，我们只能
encourage it but we can at least make
鼓励它，但我们至少可以使
everyone whether they're an expert
每个人都是专家
developer or not aware of when they're
开发人员或不知道他们何时
using its on this gun safe so the
在这支枪上使用它是安全的，所以
command line flag is by design a little
命令行标志是设计使然
bit ugly but it works just a second
有点难看，但仅需一秒钟
Jeremy ok so as with sunless gun safe
杰里米（O）
these these internal things will be
这些这些内部的东西将是
unsupported they will be subject to
不支持他们将受到
change without notice but you will be
更改，恕不另行通知，但您会
able to get to them question
能够向他们提问
German
德语
open to other suggestions so it's it's
对其他建议持开放态度，就是这样
it's it's really about being explicit
这真的是要明确
and making sure that people understand
并确保人们了解
when they are building a house or a
当他们盖房子或
skyscraper on shifting sands well if
摩天大楼在流沙好，如果
they're if they're running code if for
他们是如果他们正在运行代码
example you know they're in DevOps or
例如，您知道他们在DevOps或
something well they're probably
好东西，他们可能
responsible for keeping that code
负责保留该代码
running and it's arguably a good thing
跑步，这可以说是一件好事
for them to know that well when they
让他们知道他们什么时候
drop in and drop in the next JDK update
插入并放入下一个JDK更新
release something might break and that
释放可能会破裂的东西
might be why we use it in various places
也许就是为什么我们在各个地方使用它
in JRuby
在JRuby中
but we've always but you know I
但是我们一直但是你知道我
understand you know users don't know
了解您知道用户不知道
about that but I think it's it's
关于这个，但我认为是
irresponsible that so many of these
不负责任的是
libraries have not had
图书馆还没有
but it's all one repo so it's easy to
但这都是一个回购协议，因此很容易
change isn't isn't open-source so we've
变化不是开源的，所以我们已经
considered various alternatives you
考虑过各种选择
certainly open to other suggestions I
当然可以接受其他建议
mean when obvious one is well you just
意思是当明显的人很好时
print a warning every time but
每次都打印警告
historically we've never printed we've
历史上我们从未印刷过
never had the runtime print warnings and
从来没有运行时打印警告和
this so that there there's always been a
这样，总会有一个
been a certain resistance to that so
对此有一定的抵抗力
there are more questions cliff
还有更多的问题悬崖
so basically just accept that we're
所以基本上就是接受我们
trapped in the vortex n' and be done
被困在漩涡n'中并完成
yeah
是的
so what Paul has has stuff to talk about
保罗有话要说
as well so we're gonna have workshop
还有我们要去工作坊
time after this we can get get into this
在此之后的时间，我们可以进入
in further depth for now let me let me
现在让我更深入
just leave you with the notice that yeah
只是留下你的注意，是的
you shouldn't believe a word I said and
你不应该相信我说的一句话
I didn't make those images thank you
我没拍那些照片谢谢